I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you, I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame
We were all swept away
I'll come and get you; I'm armed, always ready to fight
Don't take all of the weight
You always do
There will always be something you cannot control
So don't take all of the blame
We will overcome. Your salvation has begun
We're wrong as well
Oh, wait, don't take all of the weight
You always do
No signs, no lights
There will always be something you cannot control
Such a mess all over
We will overcome
Don't kill your hopes
Your salvation has begun
You make me realize who I need
No sounds, no light
Such a mess all over
I'll be there, hold on
Don't kill your hopes
They'll change you somehow
You make me realize who I need
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
I'll be there, hold on
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
They'll change us somehow
So where are you now?
The fallen angels you run with don't know
I'll reach you by dawn
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
The shadows appear
Illusions so bright
Torn old sepia photographs show
To fall and then just to run
Our fragile preious world
Let them know it is the pain that makes us so human after all
Must discard it, respond to the call
Don't want to deceive me, you follow the truth
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 i.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
日听:鱼子酱&paper   翻译:小悠&冰蝶   校对:夜神&Lucifer   时间轴:阿水   压制:久嘉
You found your precious world, but discard it, respond to the call
Contract
with the Black Demon
We nobles with Progenitor blood are gathered here today for one reason: a new threat!
今日　始祖の血を継ぐ貴族の方々に集まってもらったのは他でもない
脅威
Running rampant across the whole of Northern Tokyo
それは東京以北において暴れている
「日本帝鬼軍」という名の人間どもの組織だ
is a human organization called
the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
奴らは我らの同胞を殺し
They are killing our brothers and sisters,
expanding their territory,
A human organization.
人間の…組織…
領土を拡大し　欲望のままに禁忌の呪法に手を出す
and flirting with forbidden magic as they desire.
情報では再び「終わりの天使」の実験までしているという
セラフ
According to our intel, they are once again experimenting on the Seraphs of the End.
このまま奴らを野放しにしておけば
If we leave them as they are,
8年前と同じ　大厄災が起きることは間違いない
a plague like that of eight years ago
will break out once more.
Therefore...
よって我らは
「日本帝鬼軍」を殲滅することに決めた
we have decided to crush
the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
This is war.
戦争だ
We will wipe out the corrupt humans
so that this world's balance may be preserved!
世界の安定を守るため
我らは欲深い人間どもを　皆殺しにする
戦争…
War, and the Seraphs of the End...
終わりの天使
セラフ
Yuu...
優ちゃん　すぐ助けに行くからね…
I'll rescue you soon.
That concludes my report for Block 3.
第三区画の報告は　以上です
Hiiragi Shinya, Major General of the
Japanese Imperial Demon Army, reporting.
日本帝鬼軍　少将　柊深夜です
関西方面の吸血鬼たちが不穏な動きを見せているとの情報について報告します
I will be addressing the concerns of suspicious vampire activity within the Kansai region.
Ichinose.
一瀬
Hey, Ichinose Guren!
おい　一瀬グレン
Is this drag of a meeting over yet?
クソ長え会議は終わったか
Watch your tongue.
その態度は何だ
一瀬家の分際で…
You are but a mere Ichinose.
Ah, the great General Hiiragi Tenri.
これは柊天利様　失礼致しました
Please do excuse me.
なんせひどく退屈だったもので
I was just so bored I couldn't contain myself.
Ingrate.
貴様　いい気になるのも…
Don't get ahead of yourself—
Now, now.
まあまあ　彼の態度は　いつものことでしょう
This is standard fare for him.
報告を続きます
I'll continue with my report.
I'm outta here.
俺行くわ
Just forward the minutes to me later or something.
情報は後でまとめてくれよ
ちょっとグレン
Come on, Guren.
あんまり態度悪いと　さすがの僕もフォローしきれないんだけど
Even I can't defend you if you behave that poorly.
誰がフォロー頼んだっけ
I don't recall asking you to.
Sheesh.
もぉ…
それに　この日本帝鬼軍はお偉い柊家様たちが牛耳ってるんだ
The almighty Hiiragi family are the ones who hold the reins of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
なら分家の一瀬家はお呼びじゃないだろう
The Ichinose branch family is hardly needed here, no?
So you do know your place.
よく分ってるじゃねえか
ならさっさと消えろよ　クズ
Show your ugly mug out already, scum.
What does it look like I'm doing?
だから消えるっつってんだろ
Later.
じゃあな
Jeez, that was stuffy as hell.
クソつまんなかった
I've finally found you, Guren!
馬鹿グレン見つけたぁああああ
相変わらずお前　分かりやすいなあ
Still as direct as ever, I see.
くだらん政治の後だと　ちょっと面白いぞ
It's rather amusing,
especially after a round of inane politics.
It's not funny!
面白くねぇよ
What's with you completely vanishing
for ten days without handing me an Infernal Arm?!
鬼呪装備渡さないで10日も失踪するってどういうことだ
お前　そーんなに吸血鬼に復讐したいのか
Are you really that desperate for revenge?
Of course I am!
したいね　俺はそのためだけに生きてんだよ
It's the only thing I live for!
The only thing, huh?
そのためだけにねぇ…
まぁ　あんまり長くこいつをここに置いといて
Well, I don't want to keep him here for so long that it'd attract the Hiiragis' attention.
柊家の奴らに目ぇ付けられるのもなんだしな…
よし　なら鬼と契約するか
All right, then.
Let's have you form a contract with a demon,
で　前線に出してやる
and I'll ship you off to the front lines.
え　マジで
What? For real?!
Sure, why not?
ああ　そうしよう
I don't care if you haven't completed your training.
訓練間に合ってなくてもいいや
死んだらお前の責任な
Dying is your problem, not mine.
It'll be no problem at all!
問題ないね
Hell yeah, I've been waiting for something like this!
そうだよ　そういう展開をずっと待ってたんだよ
やっぱ馬鹿だなお前
You really are a dumbass.
Oh, by the way, Yuu.
ところでさ　優
Yeah?
Stop trying to hit your superiors, moron!
上官蹴ろうとするんじゃねぇえええ
Man, it's hard work dealing with idiots.
やっぱ馬鹿どもの相手すんのは疲れるわ
でもまっ　ちょっと面白くなってきたな
But even so, I suppose this is
a rather interesting turn of events.
頭どうしたんです
Is something wrong with your head?
授業サボってまた喧嘩でもしてたんですか
Did you skip class and get into another fight?
Nah.
違ぇよ
グレン中佐は加減を知りませんからねぇ
Lieutenant Colonel Guren just can't help himself.
Sheesh. Don't ask about stuff you already know.
んだよ　知ってんなら聞くなよ
よかったですね
Congratulations.
鬼との契約　お許しをもらえたんでしょ
On your contract with a demon, that is.
He approved it, right?
まだ分かんねぇぞ
Who knows? That moron's as fickle as ever.
あの馬鹿は気まぐれだからなぁ
またまた　本当は嬉しいくせに
Aw, c'mon.
I know you're all happy on the inside.
Says who?
うるせぇな
でも大丈夫ですよ
I wouldn't worry too much.
グレン中佐は口は悪いし　すぐに暴力を振るいますが
He may be harsh and violent,
約束は守る人ですから
but he always keeps his promises.
ああ　ようやくだ
Yeah.
Finally...
ようやく吸血鬼どもを…
Finally, I can kill those bloodsuckers!
ようやくですねぇ
Finally, huh?
Aren't you happy?
嬉しくないんですか
ようやく君の大切な天使くんに会えるかもしれないのに
You might finally be able to meet your precious angel.
君には期待してますよ　ミカくん
I have high hopes for you, Mika.
Hey, hurry up!
ね　早く…
Oh...
It's all right.
大丈夫だよ
はい　皆さん
Okay, everyone!
今日は先日の筆記試験の答案を返して解散にしまーす
I'll be returning your written exam results now,
and then we can call it a day.
この結果は　これから与えられる鬼呪装備のランク決めにも影響するので
This will affect the rank of the
Infernal Arm you'll be receiving,
結果を受け止めて　次回に活かすようにしてくださいね
so please take any mistakes on board,
and improve on them for next time.
Gotcha!
させるか
You little...
てめ…
This is amazing!
すごーい　これアレじゃないですか
Is this for real?
Hey, cut it out!
おい　こらぁ
くっそ
Damn it!
They say this is a legendary score, attainable only by godlike beings!
超人にしか取れないと噂の点数じゃないですか
Shut up, and give it back already!
いいから返せこら
Hey!
Oh, my. I can't believe it!
幻のあの　あ～まさかそんな
C'mon!
Spellcraft I            Answer Sheet
Whoa, what's up with this?
何だこいつ　マジで0点だぞ
He seriously got a zero!
本当だ　すげぇ
You're right. This is amazing!
All the answers are written in hiragana, too.
答え全部ひらがなで書いてあるだけど
てんめぇ　いじめっ子すぎるだろ
You've got a real mean streak, you know that?
My, whatever do you mean?
いじめっ子とは何ですか
クラスに溶け込めないあなたを　人気者にしたあげてるだけじゃないですか
I'm just trying to make you popular,
since you're struggling to fit in and all.
余計なお世話だっつの
I never asked you to!
Besides, you don't need comrades or friends to kill vampires!
だいたい　仲間やら友達やらは　吸血鬼殺すのにいらねぇんだよ
まーたそんなことを
That nonsense again?
You won't be able to succeed
in the army without teamwork.
チームプレイできない人は　軍じゃ活躍できませんよ
Sure I can!
できるね
俺はスーパー活躍するね
You could even say I'll supersede!
You're so childish.
子供ですかあなたは
Who are you calling childish?!
誰が子供だって
C'mon, you guys.
まあまあ二人とも
Yuu's... Well, he was imprisoned
in the vampire capital since he was a kid,
でも優くんはあれだよね
子供の頃　吸血鬼の都市に監禁されてたから
so his English and Latin are better than
his Japanese comprehension skills, right?
読み書きは日本語より　英語やラテン語の方が得意なんだよね
There's just no helping it.
今回は仕方ないよ
Huh?
Um, yeah, you know how it is...
いや　なんつーか
Is there nothing in that tiny brain of yours?
頭にクソでも詰まってんのか
What?!
You got a problem?
何だよ
Let's see your score then, asshole!
じゃあ偉そうにしてるてめぇは何点だったんだよ
You must've scored real good, huh?!
さぞやいい点なんだろうな
From the bottom:
右から　ラテン語呪術　英語呪術　日本語呪術
Spellcraft I
Answer Sheet
Latin, English, and Japanese spellcraft.
Spellcraft I
Answer Sheet
Y'know, I'm not that good in languages other than Japanese,
いやー俺は日本語以外苦手だから
帰国子女気取りの優さんには　とても敵いませんよ
so I'm obviously no match
for a linguistic expert like you.
I'll kill you before I get to the vampires!
てねぇは吸血鬼の前にぶっ殺す
Yeah? Bring it on!
上等だ　来いやこらぁ
Cut it out, guys!
ちょっ　やめなよ
はーい　皆さん　まだ授業中ですよ
Settle down, everyone! Class isn't over yet.
You shouldn't do that!
なんだ　相変わらずクソうるせぇな　ここは
What's going on?
It's always so damn loud in here.
Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
グレン様　お帰りになったんですね
Isn't that enough?
You've returned.
Oh, Sayuri.
小百合か　帰った
Yeah, for now.
つかなんだ　この騒ぎは
What's with all the commotion?
それが…
Well...
Those two again?
ま～たあいつらか
おい　君月待て　グレンの馬鹿がいるぞ
Hold up, Kimizuki.
Guren's here.
Hey, Guren!
おい　グレン　てめぇ鬼呪装備くれんじゃなかったのかよ
What happened to giving me an Infernal Arm?
How long do I—
いつまでこんなこと…
Stop yelling, moron. I'll do the talking.
騒ぐな馬鹿　俺が喋る
一瀬中佐　説明してもらいましょうか
Lieutenant Colonel Ichinose, please explain yourself.
Why did you abandon your class
and disappear for more than ten days?
なぜクラスを放置して　十日以上も失踪したのでしょうか
I believe we now have enough ability
to form contracts for the Infernal Arms.
我々にはもう　鬼呪装備契約のための実力はあると思いますが
Oh?
You think you shitheads are ready for the real thing?
お前らグズどもに鬼と契約出来るだけの実力があるって
Damn straight I do!
あるに決まってんだろう
君月のクソにはないにしても　俺にはある
I don't know about Kimizuki, but I sure as hell am!
You shut your mouth!
てめぇは黙れよ
Take your own damn advice!
てめぇこそ黙れ
So?
んで　実際こいつら鬼の誘惑に耐えられるのか
Have they really built up a resistance to a demon's temptation?
Hm.
Well, at the very least, those two
are far stronger than I was at sixteen.
少なくともあの二人は私が16歳の頃より全然強いですけどね
他のやつらは
And the rest of them?
Surprisingly, the student who has
the highest stability against demons
意外ですが　鬼に対する安定度は
圧倒的に早乙女与一君です
is Saotome Yoichi.
Oh?
All right, then.
じゃあま　めんどいの嫌いだし
I'm not a fan of complicating things,
いっちょ試してみっか
so let's give this a shot.
W-Wait. You can't be serious, Lieutenant Colonel Guren!
ちょちょうそ　グレン様
Oh, what's this?
ありゃ　まさか中佐攻撃するつもりですか
Surely you don't intend to attack them,
Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
If you die...
死んだ奴は　修練足りてなかった自分を恨め
blame it on yourselves for not training hard enough!
What?
Wh-What is this?
な…なんだ　これ
It's as if something's crushing my heart...
し…心臓が締め付けられ
Wait. What?
What's wrong with everyone?
みんな　どうしたの
All done!
はい　終了
Now, those of you who are still conscious:
よーし　じゃ今意識がある奴
You have what it takes.
お前らは見込みありだ
このまま訓練続けてきゃ　鬼呪装備契約の儀に移れる可能性がある
Continue your training,
and you could very well move on
to the Infernal Arms Contract Ceremony.
あと立ってられた奴　お前らは優秀だ
Four stars to those of you who are still standing.
I'll grant you a trial for the Black Demon Series, the same rank as my sword, right now.
すぐに俺の刀と同ランク　「黒鬼」のシリーズに挑戦させてやる
Let's see. Looks like we have...
で　立ってるのは…
Yuu,
優　君月　与一
Kimizuki,
and Yoichi.
I wish you had passed out.
お前は気絶しろよ
Looking so relaxed without even using a ward...
呪符なしで余裕な顔しやがって
I suppose I should expect no less from the head family of the Japanese Imperial Demon Army, huh?
さすが日本帝鬼軍の当主筋　柊家様ってわけか
可愛げねえぞ
What a party pooper.
Aw, really?
え～うそ　こんなに可愛いじゃないですか
But I'm, like, super cute!
Drop dead.
死ね
Let's get going already.
さっさと行くぞ
あの　グレン様
Um, Lieutenant Colonel Guren?
Ridiculous tests from you are nothing out of the ordinary, so that's fine...
無茶苦茶な試験はいつものことでいいのですが
but I don't know about giving Yoichi a trial for the Black Demon Series.
でも与一君を「黒鬼」シリーズに挑戦させるのはどうかと思います
Do you have a problem with my decision?
俺の決定に文句あんのか
Not a problem per se,
文句はないのですが
but he just doesn't have the strength to accept a demon—
しかし彼に鬼を受け入れるだけの強さは
What?
If he's not strong enough, then he dies.
強さがなきゃ死ぬ　ここはそういう世界だろ
That's the kind of world we live in.
This isn't a game.
おままごとやってんじゃねぇぞ
But even so...
ですが…
うるせぇなぁ
Oh, be quiet already.
おい　与一
Hey, Yoichi.
お前吸血鬼に殺された　姉貴の復讐したいんだろ
You want to avenge your sister,
who was killed by a vampire, right?
Oh, um...
え　あの…
なら　命懸けるよな
So you'd be willing to put your life on the line, no?
M-My life?
い…命
Or would you rather quit?
それともやめるか
You may leave if you're afraid of dying.
死ぬのが怖きゃ帰っていいぞ
帰れ　与一
Go home, Yoichi.
Nice guys like you don't belong here.
ここはお前みたいに優しい奴がいる場所じゃねぇよ
俺も同意見だ　帰った方がいい
I agree.
You should go back.
No matter how hard I try not to, I can still hear it.
いくら耳を塞いても聞こえてくる
I'm still in that very same place.
僕はまだ　あそこに居る
Are you listening, Yoichi?
聞いてんのか　与一　お前は…
You—
Lieutenant Colonel Guren.
グレン中佐　僕やります
I'll do it.
Because I want to become stronger!
もっと強い力が欲しいから
I don't want to lose anybody close to me ever again!
もう大切な人を失わないで済むだけの力が欲しいから
くそ　こいつも結局俺と同じか
Well, shit.
In the end, he's just like me.
Then let's move.
よーし　ならさっさと行くか
We'll proceed into the Contract Ceremony.
契約の儀式に移んぞ
今更ビビだってしょうがねぇだろう
There's no use getting cold feet now.
Uh...
Don't look so worried.
そうなさげねぇ顔するな
You made your choice, right?
覚悟は　決めたんだろう
Yeah.
And you? How are you doing, Kimizuki?
そういう君月さんは大丈夫ですか
You may have been standing earlier,
先程は立っていられましたけど
but you had to steady yourself against a desk.
机に手　ついてましたよね
Am I right? Didn't you see it, Yoichi?
ね　与一さんも見ましたよね
Eh? Uh, yes...
え　ああ　はい
S-Stop paying attention to the little things!
こまけえとこ　見てんじゃねえよ
俺も見たぜ　君月
I saw it too, Kimizuki.
You seemed to be in a lot of pain.
お前随分苦しそうだったよな
Don't get too comfortable yourself, Yuu.
お前も余裕こいてんじゃねぇぞ　優
The demon you're going to contract with is nothing like the one you fought.
今日契約すんのは　この前の鬼とは別物だ
気抜くと一瞬で突き殺されるぞ
If you let your guard down,
it'll possess and devour you in a heartbeat.
分かってるよ
I know.
We're here.
さーて　ここだ
And where's "here," exactly?
なんだ　ここは
Where we store what you desire the most:
お前が一番欲しがっていた
weapons containing the strongest demons.
最上位の鬼神を封入した武器が集まっている部屋だよ
The strongest...
最上位の
So I can kill vampires with those?
じゃあ　それがありゃ吸血鬼を狩れんのか
そりゃお前の実力次第だな
Well, that depends on your skill.
でも　お前のと同じ奴なんだろ
But they're the same as your sword, right?
Correct.
そうだ　ここにあるのは希少な「黒鬼」シリーズだ
These are the rare Black Demon Series weapons.
まあもういいだろ　始めようぜ
But enough talk. Let's begin.
だらだらお前らに付き合うほど俺も暇じゃねぇんだよ
I have better things to do
than to fool around with you kids.
で　どうすりゃいい
So, what do we do?
Choose the weapon you like,
and step into the ritual circle.
好きな武器を選んで儀式陣に入れ
The Contract Ceremony starts
as soon as you touch a weapon.
武器に触れたら　自動で契約の儀が始まるようにできている
お前らが鬼に負けなけりゃ力が手に入る
If you triumph over the demon,
you'll acquire its power.
もし負けたら
And if you don't?
You'll either become a murderous demon yourself
人喰いの鬼になるか　鬼の力に潰されて死ぬか
or be killed by its power.
But you'll die either way, so it's not as if it matters.
でもどっちにしろ死ぬな
Because if you end up as the former, I'll kill you.
人喰い鬼になったら　俺が殺すから
I like it.
いいねえ　俺はずっとこういうの待ってたんだよ
I've been waiting for this.
馬鹿グレンがぬるぬる学校なんか行かせやがって
That dumbass Guren,
making me go to some lame school...
力を手に入れて家族を…
I'm going to become stronger and avenge my family.
I'll slaughter the vampires that took Mika from me.
ミカを殺した吸血鬼ども皆殺しにする
俺はそのためだけに生きてきたんだ
That's the only thing I've lived for!
抜け　そしたら始まる
Draw.
Then the ceremony will begin.
Give me your power, you shitty demon!
俺に力を寄越せよ　クソ鬼が
najimeta shi ni torikago sumi
Caged in the city I call home
馴染めた白　鳥がご隅　鼓動獲たツボミも
kogoeta tsubomi no okizarigoe
A frozen bud cries silently
置き去り声　眩めた　記憶の影
kurameta kioku no kage
Turning the shadows of my memories ever darker
I need your blood
i need your blood
You really love 唱える
you need love tonight
Just as you need love tonight
akaku red line
We're walking a red tightrope
足掻く　Red Light
嗅ぎ分けた音　音と
kakiwaketa neon to
As the neon lights we leave in our wake
こじ開けたReasonが
kojiaketa reason ga
And the reasons we carved out for ourselves
ただ平行に並ぶ
tada heikou ni narabu
Run parallel
Come on break it down for me!
Come and break it down for me
come and break it down for me
A river will flow
i'll lead the way home
And I'll lead the way home
KEYがない「欲しい」でも　利害鳴る鈴
i'll lead the way home
Though the shooting stars pay no heed to us
kiganai hoshi demo
negai nasazu
Leaving our wishes unfulfilled
懺悔さえ乾いた　４拍子が　奏でた意図を辿る
zange sae kawaita yogoshi ga
In a depraved world devoid of guilt
kanadetai tone nara
The tone you evoke
木漏れ日の　赤が　騒ぐ
kanadetai tone nara
Turns dusk a madder red
komorebi no aka ga sawagu
Next time on Seraph of the End:
次回　終わりのセラフ
A New
Family
"A New Family."